<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title><link>http://example.org/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 03:46:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My First Post</title><link>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 03:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/my-first-post/my-first-post/</guid><description>Hello, Hugo! 🐝</description></item><item><title>Github Actions and Snowflake Integration</title><link>http://example.org/posts/2021-10-31-githubactions-snowflake/2021-10-31-githubactions-snowflake/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 18:19:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/2021-10-31-githubactions-snowflake/2021-10-31-githubactions-snowflake/</guid><description>GitHub Actions and Snowflake Integration The objective of this article is to explore CICD (Continuous Integration / Continuous Deployment) for our data modelling using Github actions and Snowflake data platform.
The benefit of applying CICD concept on your data model is to keep traceability of your model and easy deployment to your data platform, which in this case is Snowflake.
GitHub is used as a repository for the data model. The data model is a collection of sql queries used to generated tables and views.</description></item><item><title>Generative Deep Learning</title><link>http://example.org/posts/2021-09-22-generative-deep-learning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 09:19:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/2021-09-22-generative-deep-learning/</guid><description>Generative Deep Learning This repository is intended as place to keep my current experimentations on generative deep learning using tensorflow.
Most of the code is based on the Coursera course Generative Deep Learning with TensorFlow by Laurence Moroney and Eddy Shyu.
Check notebook here.
Fast Neural Style Transfer Paper describing Fast Neural Style Transfer can be found here.
The model is provided by Tensorflow Hub.
Figure below illustrate the main concept of Neural Style Transfer, which is based on the paper A Neural Algorithm of Artistic Style (Gatys, Ecker &amp;amp; Bethge, 2015).</description></item></channel></rss>